Guide to the Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 1, Section 3: Boxes 45-66
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 1, Section 3: Boxes 45-66
- Box: 62, Folder: 5 (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Item 21: General Motors Reply to UAW-CIO Brief Submitted in Support of Wage Demand for 52 Hours Pay for 40 Hours Work, Publication (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Item 22: Five Years of Industrial Peace, Publication (Box 62, Folder 5)
- Box: 62, Folder: 6 (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Quality of Work Life, Publication (Box 62, Folder 6)
    By Ted Mills. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Selling to General Motors, Publication (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: Controls or Collective Bargaining - Restraints and Realities, Publication (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Item 4: Employee Asessement, Publication (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Item 5: Standard Apprentice Plan, Publication (Box 62, Folder 6)
    By General Motors; UAW. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Your Blue Cross And Blue Shield National Account Program Benefits, Publication (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Item 7: Automobiles- Largest Tax Source, Publication (Box 62, Folder 6)
    By UAW. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Pontiac Builds Reserve Parts Awaiting 'Go' Signal, Publication (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Item 9: The Well of Idleness, Publication (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Item 10: Working Conditions In The Motor Industry, Publication (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Item 11: Strategy, Publication (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Item 12: General Motors Strike, Publication (Box 62, Folder 6)
    By Trade Union Committee Of the GM Strike. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: It's Time To Set The Record Straight, Publication (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Item 14: General Motors: beyond the marketplace, Publication (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Item 15: Information Handbook A Ready Reference For the News Media, Publication (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Item 16: Working with General Motors, Publication (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Item 17: Your Key To Progress, Publication (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Item 18: Annual Purchasing Power of Auto Workers At All-Time High In 1936, Publication (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Item 19: Industrial Relations Staff, Publication (Box 62, Folder 6)
- Box: 63, Folder: 1 (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Sixteen Years of Progress Through Free Collective Bargaining, Publication (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Press Release Tuesday May 25, 1948, Publication (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Looking Forward in Labor Relations: a talk, Publication (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Free Collective Bargaining Works!: A Record of Progress, Publication (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: Legislation for Labor Peace, Publication (Box 63, Folder 1)
    By C. E. Wilson. February 5 Statement before U.S. Senate Committee on Labor and Public Welfare. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: The Development and Growth of General Motors, Publication (Box 63, Folder 1)
    By Harlow H. Curtice. Statement before Subcommittee on Antitrust and Monopoly of the U.S. Senate Committee on the Judiciary. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Is It Scientific?, Publication (Box 63, Folder 1)
    By Customer Research Staff. Detroit Michigan. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: The Top Third, Publication (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Item 9: The Organization of General Motors Corporation, Publication (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Item 10: Remarks at the 43rd Annual Meeting California State Chamber of Commerce, Publication (Box 63, Folder 1)
    By James M. Roche. Thursday, January 21. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Letter April 28, Publication (Box 63, Folder 1)
    By D. F. Neubauer. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: The Organization of General Motors Corporation, Publication (Box 63, Folder 1)
    By William M. Collins. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Address before the Flint Michigan Rotary Club, Publication (Box 63, Folder 1)
    By George B. Morris, Jr.. September 22. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: General Motors Policies and Progress, Publication (Box 63, Folder 1)
    By General Electric. February 16. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Clarke GM Diesel, Inc. Company Rules, Publication (Box 63, Folder 1)
    By R. D. Hachey. January 24. Item is in English.
- Box: 63, Folder: 2 (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Organization Structure, Policies and Procedures and Basic Management Training, Publication (Box 63, Folder 2)
    By General Motors Institute; General Motors. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: General Motors Employes Retirement Plan, Publication (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Negro Education: A Key to Equality, Publication (Box 63, Folder 2)
    By James M. Roche. An Address at the United Negro College Fund Alumni Luncheon. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Management Priorities for the 1970's, Publication (Box 63, Folder 2)
    By Edward N. Cole. April 10. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Hiring Manual "Complete Job-Tests Program, Publication (Box 63, Folder 2)
    By Programs for Personnel Measurement. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: a look at General Motors, Publication (Box 63, Folder 2)
- Box: 63, Folder: 3 (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Problems Industry Faces in the Months Ahead, Publication (Box 63, Folder 3)
    By C. E. Wilson. December 10,. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Personnel Policies, Publication (Box 63, Folder 3)
    By C. E. Wilson. Address at the meeting of the General Motors Men's Club, held in Detroit, Michigan on November 13. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: General Motors Corporation News, Publication (Box 63, Folder 3)
    By General Motors. Tuesday, May 25. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Statement by Counsel for Gneral Motors Corporation in N.L.R.B Proceeding, Publication (Box 63, Folder 3)
    By A. F. Power. February 6. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Statement before United States Senate Committee on Labor and Public Welfare, Publication (Box 63, Folder 3)
    By C. E. Wilson. Wednesday, February 5. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: The Development and Growth of General Motors, Publication (Box 63, Folder 3)
    By Harlow H. Curtice. Statement before Subcommittee on Antitrust and Monopoly of the U.S. Senate Committee on the Judiciary, Friday, December 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: General Motors Public Interest Report 1977-78, Publication (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Item 8: Technical Bulletin No. 7: Critical Comments on the "Your Job" Questionnaire, Publication (Box 63, Folder 3)
    By Empoye Research Section. Results of a survey of industrial psychologists and personnel men requesting critical comments on an experimental questionnaire approach. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Judging Procedure for the "My Job and Why I Like It" Contest, Publication (Box 63, Folder 3)
    By General Motors Emplyoe Relations Staff. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Your Job, Publication (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Item 11: Experience Tells Me, Publication (Box 63, Folder 3)
    By J. J. Cronin. Talk at the Annual Slide Rule Dinner of University of Detroit Engineering Students March 26. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Speech to United States Conferene of Mayors, Publication (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Item 13: Helping Dealers make more and better friends for themselves and for general motors, Publication (Box 63, Folder 3)
    By General Electric. A Communitiy Relations Program for General Motors Dealers. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: General Motors Overseas: An International Colossus Whose Evolution Has Brought Forth a Whole Philosophy of Foreign Trade, Publication (Box 63, Folder 3)
    By General Electric. Fortune magazine for November. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Industry's Number One Problem Defined, Publication (Box 63, Folder 3)
    By Paul Garrett. February 9. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: General Motors' Statement Before Fact-Finding Board, Publication (Box 63, Folder 3)
    By Walter Gordon Merritt. Statement in behalf of General Motors was presented in Washtington on December 28 before the Fact-Finding Board in the General Motors--UAW-CIO dispute. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: Problems of Industrial Organization and Control, Publication (Box 63, Folder 3)
    By Donaldson Brown. Nobember 16. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: Industrial Management As a National Resource, Publication (Box 63, Folder 3)
    By Donaldson Brown. March 18. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: Problems of Industrial Organization and Control, Publication (Box 63, Folder 3)
    By Donaldson Brown. November 16. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: The Work We Live By Vo.ume 12, Publication (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Item 21: Sixteen Years of Progress Through Free Collective Bargaining, Publication (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Item 22: General Motors builds its first 50 Million Cars, Publication (Box 63, Folder 3)
    By Department of Public Relations. Item is in English.
  - Item 23: Short Wave Broadcast, Publication (Box 63, Folder 3)
    By Alfred P. Sloan, Jr.. Item is in English; Russian.
  - Item 24: Importance of Jobs, Publication (Box 63, Folder 3)
    By Alfred P. Sloan, Jr.. Nobember 15. Item is in English; Russian.
  - Item 25: The General Motors Strike - The Facts and Their Implications: Against Group Compulsion, Publication (Box 63, Folder 3)
    By Alfred P. Sloan, Jr.. April 18. Item is in English.
  - Item 26: The General Motors Strike - The Facts and their Implications: Managerial Responsibilities, Publication (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Item 27: Why the Confusion? Free Competition and Exercise of Individual Initiative, Publication (Box 63, Folder 3)
    By Alfred P. Sloan, Jr.. November 13. Item is in English.
  - Item 28: Opposed to Industry-Wide Control or Planning, Publication (Box 63, Folder 3)
    By C. E. Wilson. Press Conference Transcipt April 30. Item is in English.
  - Item 29: War Effort -- Pooling Ideas, Technical Information, and Tools, Publication (Box 63, Folder 3)
    By C. E. Wilson. Radio interview with Fulton Lewis, Jr., on January 22. Item is in English.
  - Item 30: The Automotive Industry, War and Postwar: Social Philosophy, Publication (Box 63, Folder 3)
    By C. E. Wilson. October 1945. Item is in English.
  - Item 31: Social Philosophy, Publication (Box 63, Folder 3)
    By C. E. Wilson. Talk at centennial celebration of Mount Union College, October 18. Item is in English.
  - Item 32: Economic Policies, Publication (Box 63, Folder 3)
    By C. E. Wilson. Address at the meeting of the General Motors Men's Club, held at the Masonic Temple, November 13. Item is in English.
  - Item 33: General Motors Corporation Electro-Motive Division UAW-CIO bargaining Meeting, Publication (Box 63, Folder 3)
    By General Motors. May 29 Grievance Procedures. Item is in English.
  - Item 34: Report on Operation of Suggestion Plan, Publication (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Item 35: General Motors Policies and Practices, Publication (Box 63, Folder 3)
    By Harlow H. Curtice. before U.S. Senate Committee on Banking and Currency, March 18. Item is in English.
  - Item 36: Suggested Letter to Foremen, Publication (Box 63, Folder 3)
    By Plant Manager. 2 advertisement clippings included: "Do You Want This General Motors Book?" and "If you are interested in Airplane Power". Item is in English.
  - Item 37: Your 1945 War Chest Campaign, Publication (Box 63, Folder 3)
    By Employe Cooperation Staff. Item is in English.
  - Item 38: Letters to Dr. Burns, Publication (Box 63, Folder 3)
    By Rosie. 2 short notes, attached to next pamphlet in folder. Item is in English.
  - Item 39: Employe Rating, Publication (Box 63, Folder 3)
    By Education & Training Dept., Personnel Division. Item is in English.
  - Item 40: Shall We Have More -- Or Less?, Publication (Box 63, Folder 3)
    By Alfred P. Sloan, Jr.. May 22. Item is in English.
  - Item 41: More and Better Jobs: Technological Change, Publication (Box 63, Folder 3)
    By Alfred P. Sloan, Jr.. May 25. Item is in English.
  - Item 42: Which Way?: Capitalize Industrial Change in Interest of All Groups, Publication (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Item 43: The Challenge: Economic Statesmanship, Publication (Box 63, Folder 3)
    By Alfred P. Sloan, Jr.. December 10. Item is in English.
  - Item 44: Unionization of Management, Publication (Box 63, Folder 3)
    By H. W. Anderson. Talk before General Motors Club of Indianapolis, June 6. Item is in English.
- Box: 63, Folder: 4 (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: American Battle for Abundance: A Story of Mass Production, Publication (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Word Wide Competition -- Can U.S. Business Meet The Challenge?, Publication (Box 63, Folder 4)
    By Elliot M. Estes. Address before the Executive Dinner Forum of the Wharton Entrepreneurial Center, March 1. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Management Skill in Job Training and Job Improvement, Publication (Box 63, Folder 4)
    By General Motors Institute. Basic Management Training. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: The New Work Force Program Materials: A General Motors Management Training Program, Publication (Box 63, Folder 4)
    By General Motors Institute. Enclosed is a letter by Chester A. Francke, June 17. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Meeting the Challenge Ahead, Publication (Box 63, Folder 4)
    By Harlow H. Curtice. Delivered before the Luncheon for Business Leaders at GM Motorama, on Tuesday, January 19. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Press Conference GM Motorama 1955 Remarks, Publication (Box 63, Folder 4)
    By Harlow H. Curtice. January 18. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Is America Ready for the Eighties, Publication (Box 63, Folder 4)
    By Thomas A. Murphy. at the National Coal Association Conference, June 22. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Individual Freedom Versus Economic Planning, Publication (Box 63, Folder 4)
    By Thomas A. Murphy. Remarks before Greater Detroit Chamber of Commerce Annual Meeting Banquet, June 5. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: What Ever Happened to E Pluribus Unum, Publication (Box 63, Folder 4)
    By Thomas A. Murphy. at the Economic Club of Detroit, October 9. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Freedom, Profits and Ethics, Publication (Box 63, Folder 4)
    By Thomas A. Murphy. An Address before the Chamber of Commerce, May 1. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Five Years of Industrial Peace, Publication (Box 63, Folder 4)
    By C. E. Wilson. A discussion of the five-year Agreement between General Motors and the UAW-CIO. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Clippings on UAW-CIO-Management parley on causes of retarded auto production, Publication (Box 63, Folder 4)
    By General Motors. In Folder addressed to Dr. Robert K. Burns. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: University of Michigan Annual Business Leadership Lecture, Publication (Box 63, Folder 4)
    By Thomas A. Murphy. February 19. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: As Johnny Comes Marching Home, Publication (Box 63, Folder 4)
    By AC Spark Plug Division. Placement and Follow-Up Plan in Operations. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: General Motor Statement Regarding Union's Proposal To Amend Paragraph 63 of the March 19, 1946 National Agreement, Publication (Box 63, Folder 4)
    By General Motors. April 14. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Conference for Educators Held at General Motors Building, Publication (Box 63, Folder 4)
    By General Motors. Afternoon Session, June 27. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: When does 90 days = 30 Years?, Publication (Box 63, Folder 4)
    By Employe Research Section. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: An Analysis of the Paid Sick Leave Leave Plan for Hourly-Rated Factory Workers, Publication (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Item 19: Dparmental Functions and Interrelationships, Publication (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Item 20: Management Skill in Working with People, Publication (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Item 21: The Job of First Line Management, Publication (Box 63, Folder 4)
- Box: 63, Folder: 5 (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Techniques of Employment Interviewing, Publication (Box 63, Folder 5)
    By Personnel Staff; General Motors Institute. Basic Reference Manual. Item is in English.
- Box: 63, Folder: 6 (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Accident Prevention - A Major Activity in General Motors, Publication (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: Frequency and Severity figures, Publication (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: 1945 Annual Safety Report for General Motors Corporation, Publication (Box 63, Folder 6)
    By Personnel Staff, Personnel Departments, Service Activities. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Safety Report for Gneral Motors Corporation, Publication (Box 63, Folder 6)
    By Personnel Staff, Personnel Deparments, Service Activities. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Safety At Work, Publication (Box 63, Folder 6)
    By D. T. Mould. Safety Idea Exchange Bulletin 337, November 15. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Fatal Accident, Publication (Box 63, Folder 6)
    By D. T. Mould. Safety Idea Exchange Bulletin 392, May 17. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Near Serious Acid Injury, Publication (Box 63, Folder 6)
    By D. T. Mould. Safety Idea Exchange Bulletin 344, June 25. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Unsafe Conditions, Publication (Box 63, Folder 6)
    By D. T. Mould. Safety Idea Exchange Bulletin 352, July 24. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: An Eye Was Saved With Safety Glasses, Publication (Box 63, Folder 6)
    By D. T. Mould. Safety Idea Exchange 238, September 9. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Description of punch presses, Publication (Box 63, Folder 6)
- Box: 63, Folder: 7 (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: A Handbook for Foremen, Publication (Box 63, Folder 7)
    By Education & Training Department. Item is in English.
- Box: 63, Folder: 8 (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Techniques of Employment Investigation, Publication (Box 63, Folder 8)
    By Personnel Staff. Basic Reference Material. Item is in English.
- Box: 63, Folder: 9 (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Supervisors Performance Review Handbook, Publication (Box 63, Folder 9)
    By American Institute for Research and The Personnel Staff. Item is in English.
- Box: 63, Folder: 10 (Box 63, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Automotive Daily News, Publication (Box 63, Folder 10)
    By General Motors. 2nd Strike Issue February 9. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: General Motors and Its Labor Policy, Publication (Box 63, Folder 10)
    By Alfred P. Sloan, Jr.. statement to the employes of all General Motors domestic manufacturing operations was posted in all plants of the Corporation in the United States on January 5. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: How Members of the General Motors Family are made Partners in General Motors, Publication (Box 63, Folder 10)
    By Alfred P. Sloan, Jr.. Message to Stockholders. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: They Fight Their Battle Sitting Down, Publication (Box 63, Folder 10)
    By Herbert Harris. Where and When Did American Labor Learn the Effectiveness of Passive Resistance?, February 6. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Report on Employe's Opinion, Publication (Box 63, Folder 10)
    By General Motors. Employe Research Report No. 43. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Memorandum on General Motors Profits, Publication (Box 63, Folder 10)
    By General Motors. January 31. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Expanding Employment: The Answer to Unemployment, Publication (Box 63, Folder 10)
  - Item 8: Inflation -- or Production, Publication (Box 63, Folder 10)
    By Henry J. Taylor. No. 3 of a series of radio talks sponsored by General Motors Corporation, broadcast December 28. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Five Years of Industrial Peace, Publication (Box 63, Folder 10)
  - Item 10: American Battle for Abundance: A Story of Mass Production, Publication (Box 63, Folder 10)
    By Charles Franklin Kettering; Allen Orth. c. 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: A Report of National Citizens Committeee on GM--UAW-CIO Dispute, Publication (Box 63, Folder 10)
    By Henry H. Crane. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Comments on GM's Five-Year Contract, Publication (Box 63, Folder 10)
    By Department of Public Relations. Collection of newspaper and clippings, especially political cartoons. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: A Case Example in Public Relations, Publication (Box 63, Folder 10)
    By Paul Garrett. Delivered at the dinner meeting of the Third National Public Relations Conference, December 4. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Information Racks -- A New Effective Method of Communicating With Employes, Publication (Box 63, Folder 10)
    By William H. Lane. 5th Annual Conference, Public Relations Society of America, Inc., November 25. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: General Motors Labor Policies and Procedures, Publication (Box 63, Folder 10)
    By General Electric. 3 copies; March 25. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: A Message to Our Employes on the Progress of the Strike Situation, Publication (Box 63, Folder 10)
    By Alfred P. Sloan, Jr.. Statement to the mployees of all General Motors domestic manufacturing operations posted in all plants of the Corporation in the United States on January 27. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: A Message to General Motors Employes, Publication (Box 63, Folder 10)
    By Alfred P. Sloan, Jr.. March 1. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: General Motors and the Strike Conference, Publication (Box 63, Folder 10)
    By William S. Knudsen; Donaldson Brown; John Thomas Smith. Statement to the Public issued February 8. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: The Story of the General Motors Strike, Publication (Box 63, Folder 10)
    By Alfred P. Sloan, Jr.. Submitted to Stockholders, April. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: General Motors and Its Labor Policy, Publication (Box 63, Folder 10)
    By Alfred P. Sloan, Jr.. Statement to the employes of all General Motors domestic manufacturing operations posted in all plants of the Corporation in the United States on January 5. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: The Worker in General Motors, Publication (Box 63, Folder 10)
    By Alfred P. Sloan, Jr.. Statement to stockholders December 31. Item is in English.
  - Item 22: Labor Relations in General Motors, Publication (Box 63, Folder 10)
  - Item 23: Employe Relations in General Motors, Publication (Box 63, Folder 10)
    By Employe Relations Staff. May1. Item is in English.
- Box: 63, Folder: 11 (Box 63, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Working with General Motors: A Handbook for Salaried Men and Women, Publication (Box 63, Folder 11)
  - Item 2: Post-War Jobs, Publication (Box 63, Folder 11)
    By Alfred P. Sloan, Jr.. Address at opening Fall Session of the Economic Club of Detroit, October 11. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Should Management Be Unionized, Publication (Box 63, Folder 11)
  - Item 4: A Six Point Objective for General Motors, Publication (Box 63, Folder 11)
    By C. E. Wilson. Statement to GM executives. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: One to One: a formula for individual involvement in improving urban life, Publication (Box 63, Folder 11)
    By Public Relations Staff. A "Help Yourself" Booklet offerd to GM Men and Women. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Toward a New Partnership, Publication (Box 63, Folder 11)
    By Roger B. Smith. Remarks at the Conference on Business and Government at the Lyndon Baines Johnson Library, March 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: For Your Retirement, Publication (Box 63, Folder 11)
    By C. E. Wilson. The General Motors Retirement Program for Salaried Employes, October 1. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Letter to the Men and Women of General Motors Represented by the UAW, Publication (Box 63, Folder 11)
    By John F. Gordon; Frederic G. Donner. Given to all General Motors employes represented by the UAW-AFL-CIO. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: A look at GM, Publication (Box 63, Folder 11)
    By General Electric. Given to all General Motors employes represented by the UAW-AFL- CIO. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: General Motors Instutute twenty-fifth Anniversary proceedings of the education-industry conference, the twenty-fifth Anniversary Banquet, the Institute Annual Alumni Day, Publication (Box 63, Folder 11)